# Godwin Salami

Ilorin, Kwara State, Nigeria



wellsdigit@gmail.com



+234 9077994889



linkedin.com/in/wellshub

### Summary

I am Godwin Salami, a dedicated frontend web developer with a deep-seated love for turning concepts into captivating online realities. My journey in the world of web development has been driven by a relentless pursuit of innovation and a commitment to delivering web solutions that not only meet but exceed expectations.

My mission is to create user-friendly and visually appealing websites that engage and inspire. From responsive designs to seamless user interfaces, I focus on the finer details to ensure exceptional user experiences.

### **Experience**



**HNG Internship** Sep 2023 - Present (1 month)



### Frontend Web Developer

**Probity Hub** Mar 2022 - Present (1 year 7 months)



## Frontend Web Developer

Coopify

Jul 2022 - Nov 2022 (5 months)

### **Education**



### Kwara State Polytechnic

Higher National Diploma, Computer Science Sep 2019 - Present

#### Skills

Tailwind CSS • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • HTML • Frontend • React.js • Front-End Development • Web Design • Web Development • Computer Graphics Design